WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Tansy!
Tansy! Tansy!
There you are.
I can't see her, Ramsay.
Tansy!
If you make it out
of the woods, you win!
Run, Tansy, run!
- Tansy.
- Where is she?
Tansy, Tansy, Tansy!
Good girls.
Down, girls.
Down.
Well done.
You, too.
- I only wounded her.
- You brought her down. That's what matters.
A fine shot.
Wasn't it, Reek?
A fine shot, master.
My lady.
Please, my lord.
It hurts.
Oh, sweet.
Don't cry.
It will be over soon.
She thinks she's pretty.
Let me put one
through her face.
We have to reward
the hounds, love.
They did all the hard work.
Why? I did
whatever you asked.
But you made Myranda
feel jealous.
- Me jealous of her?
-  My lord, please.
You can see that your presence
has become a bit of a problem.
Rip her!
Not so pretty now.
Your new hand, it's nicer
than the old one.
Wouldn't you agree, Pod?
Is it solid gold?
Gilded steel.
You're not eating.
Why is no one eating?
My wife wastes away and my
brother starves himself.
- I'm not hungry.
- You lost a hand,
not a stomach.
Try the boar.
Cersei can't get enough of it
since one killed Robert for her.
A toast.
To the proud
Lannister children.
The dwarf, the cripple,
and the mother of madness.
- Oh!
- I'll clean it up.
No, I'll do it.
Leave us.
It's only wine.
I can't fight anymore.
What about your left?
I can hold a sword, but all
my instincts are wrong.
How can I protect the king
when I can hardly
wipe my own ass?
You're the Lord Commander now.
Command.
Let others do the fighting.
When was the last time
Father used a sword?
I'm not Father.
I'm the Kingslayer.
When people find out
I can't slay a pigeon...
Train, then. Learn to fight
with your other hand.
With whom? You?
Men talk.
Soon as someone discovers I can't
fight, he'll tell everyone.
You need a proper,
discreet swordsman.
As it happens,
I have just the one.
My brother tells me you
can keep your mouth shut.
Unusual talent for a sellsword.
He tells me you shit gold
just like your father.
Is this place safe?
There's this knight, Leygood,
- got thunderbolts on his shield.
- Uh-huh.
Right here is where
I fuck his wife.
She's a screamer, that one.
If they don't hear her,
they won't hear us.
I've never seen
Valyrian steel before.
She's a beauty.
The problem is,
if you fight with
an edged blade,
I'll have to.
And if I fight with
an edged blade,
I'll have no one
left to pay me.
I haven't used a sparring
sword since I was nine.
Ah!
Bold warrior you are, attacking
a man when his guard's down.
Best time to attack a man.
Mind yourself.
- If I still had my right hand...
- Plan on growing it back?
Come on, then.
Open the gates!
Riders coming in!
Let's get these horses seen to!
Father.
Welcome home.
Walda, this is
Ramsay Snow, my bastard.
A pleasure, Mother.
Hello.
See that the horses are fed,
watered, and rubbed down.
And take Lady Walda
to her chambers.
This way, my lady.
Where is your prize?
With the hounds.
I'll have a look at him.
I hear you took a hand
from the Kingslayer.
Word travels.
How he screamed.
You would have loved it.
Father.
What did you do to him?
I trained him. He was a slow
learner, but he learned.
You flayed him.
Peeled a few bits.
Removed a few others.
This was Balon Greyjoy's
son and heir.
We've been flaying
our enemies for 1,000 years.
The flayed man
is on our banners.
My banners, not yours.
You're not a Bolton.
You're a Snow.
Tywin Lannister has given
me the North.
But he won't lift a finger
to help me take it.
As long as the ironborn
hold Moat Cailin,
our armies are trapped
south of the Neck.
Theon was a valuable
hostage, not your plaything.
I wanted to trade him
for Moat Cailin.
I already asked.
Lord Greyjoy refused.
Savages have no...
You sent terms to Balon
Greyjoy without my consent?
You made me acting
Lord of the Dreadfort.
I acted.
I had to smuggle myself
into my own lands
thanks to the Greyjoys.
I needed Theon.
I needed him whole.
Theon was our enemy.
But Reek,
Reek will never betray us.
I placed far too much
trust in you.
Reek, how could you let me stand
before my father unshaven?
-  It's disrespectful.
- I'm sorry, my lord.
Give him the razor.
If I'm not a Bolton,
Father, what does it matter?
Go on, Reek.
A nice close shave.
Reek, tell Father
where are Bran
and Rickon Stark?
I don't know, my lord.
You murdered them
and displayed their corpses
at Winterfell.
Reek,
did you murder the Stark boys?
No, my lord.
Just two farm boys.
And crisped them
so no one would know.
Yes, my lord.
The Starks have always
ruled the North.
If Bran and Rickon are alive,
the country will rally
to their side
now that Robb Stark is gone.
Oh, that's right, Reek.
Robb Stark is dead.
Sorry.
I know he was like
a brother to you.
But my father put a knife
through his heart.
How do you feel about that?
- You ready for a hunt?
- Always.
Find those boys and I'll give
you 1,000 acres and a holdfast.
Your pet rat have any thoughts
on which way they went
after Winterfell?
Jon Snow is at Castle Black.
Who the fuck is Jon Snow?
Their bastard brother.
He could be sheltering them.
He may know where they are.
Even if he doesn't,
he's half Stark himself.
Could be a threat.
You want to prove
yourself a Bolton?
Gather whatever men you can
and ride for Moat Cailin.
Bring this creature of yours.
Maybe he'll be of some use.
Take the Moat for the family,
for our family,
and I'll reconsider
your position.
Lord Varys. Breakfasting
with the king?
I'm afraid foreigners aren't
welcome at such exclusive affairs.
- Oh, to be foreign.
- Ahem.
Shae has been noticed.
Sansa's maid saw you with her.
She already told your sister.
It's only a matter of time
before your father hears.
So I'm guilty of being seen
with my own wife's handmaiden.
My father will ask you
if there's anything more
and you'll tell him
some clever lie.
No, I will not.
How long do you imagine your father
and sister would let me live
if they suspected me of lying?
I have no pet sellsword
to protect me.
No legendary brother
to avenge me.
Only little birds
who whisper in my ear.
Forgive me
if I don't weep for you.
No one weeps
for spiders or whores.
I have friends across
the sea who could help her.
She won't leave.
I've told her this is
a dangerous place
so many times,
she no longer believes it.
Your father has promised to hang
the next whore he finds you with.
Have you ever known your
father to make an idle threat?
From House Tyrell and the
people of the Reach,
Your Grace, it is my honor to
present you with this wedding cup.
May you
and my daughter Margaery
drink deep and live long.
A handsome goblet, my lord.
Or shall I call you Father?
I shall be honored, Your Grace.
She's the whore
I told you about.
The dark-haired one.
Have her brought to the Tower
of the Hand before the wedding.
A book?
"The Lives of Four Kings."
Grand Maester Kaeth's history
of the reigns of
Daeron the Young Dragon,
Baelor the Blessed, Aegon the
Unworthy, and Daeron the Good.
A book every king should read.
Now that the war is won,
we should all find
time for wisdom.
Thank you, Uncle.
One of only two Valyrian
steel swords in the capital,
Your Grace, freshly
forged in your honor.
Careful, Your Grace. Nothing
cuts like Valyrian steel.
So they say.
Such a great sword
should have a name.
- What shall I call her?
- Stormbringer.
- Terminus.
- Widow's Wail.
- Wolfsbane.
- Widow's Wail. I like that.
Every time I use it,
it'll be like cutting off
Ned Stark's head
all over again.
Don't.
You want me on the desk?
-  What's wrong, my lion?
- Don't call me that.
What should I call you?
I'm afraid our friendship
can't continue.
Our friendship?
There's a ship waiting in
the harbor bound for Pentos.
What?
You'll have your own
cabin, of course,
and across the Narrow Sea
a house, servants.
What is this?
I'm a married man.
My wife has suffered a great
deal, as you well know.
I don't want her to suffer
anymore on my account.
I need to uphold my vows.
She doesn't want you.
-  I need to do right by her.
- You don't want her.
By our children.
- What are you afraid of?
- I'm not afraid.
You are. You are afraid of
your father and your sister.
- You're going to run from them all your life?
- I need you to leave.
I'm not afraid of them.
I'm not going to run.
- Shae.
- We will fight them together.
It's like you said,
I am yours and you are mine.
You're a whore!
Sansa is fit to bear
my children and you are not.
I can't be in love
with a whore.
I can't have children
How many men
have you been with?
500? 5,000?
How many whores
have you been with?
I have enjoyed my time
with all of them
and I have enjoyed my time
with you most of all.
But now that time is over.
You'll have a comfortable
life in Pentos.
Bronn will escort you
to your ship.
Hear us now.
Accept these tokens
of our faith, my lord,
and lead us from the darkness.
Sire, I served you well.
Lord of Light,
show us the way...
Selyse, you're my sister!
Yours are the stars
that guide us.
Tell him!
Lord of Light, protect us,
for the night is dark
and full of terrors.
Did you see?
Their souls.
It was their souls.
Our lord took them.
Did you see?
Lord Florent was
your brother by law.
He was an infidel.
He worshipped the gods
of his fathers
and their fathers before him.
They were the gods
of your fathers, too.
I ordered him to tear
down his idols.
He disobeyed.
How many ships did he
bring to your cause?
How many men?
A good deal more than you.
Did you see, Ser Davos?
They're with our lord now.
Their sins all burned away.
Did you see?
I'm sure they're more
than grateful, my queen.
Meat's off.
Our larders are almost empty.
Serve fish, then.
We're on an island.
You hate fish.
I hate a good many things,
but I suffer them all the same.
When Storm's End was under
siege and I was starving,
Stannis boiled soup
for me from books.
The binding glue
is made from horses.
One morning, he shot two
seagulls on the beach.
I've never tasted anything
as good as grilled seagull.
- Do you remember?
- Of course I remember.
Have you ever known
true hunger, my lady?
It's all I knew
when I was a child.
Until you found
the Lord of Light?
Until he found me.
I fear for our daughter's soul.
Every mother should fear
for her child's soul.
- She's a stubborn little beast.
- She's a child.
You barely know her.
You think she's sweet because
she smiles when you visit.
She's sullen and stubborn
and sinful.
Why else would the Lord of Light
have seen fit to mark her face?
She needs the rod.
She's my daughter.
You will not strike her.
As you command.
Perhaps the Lady Melisandre
could speak with her.
Come in.
Were you sleeping, Princess?
Did you watch the ceremony
on the beach?
I heard it.
And it frightened you?
Ser Axel was my uncle.
He was always kind to me.
They're in a better
place now, Princess.
The fire cleansed them
of the sins of the world.
But they screamed.
Women scream
when they give birth.
Afterward they are
filled with joy.
Afterward they aren't
ash and bone.
You have so many
questions, don't you?
So did I when I was a child.
I was much like you.
Only I wasn't a princess.
And you didn't have this.
No.
But I suffered in other ways,
sweet girl, believe me.
What do you know of the gods?
I read
"The Seven-Pointed Star."
Lies and fables.
Septons speak of seven gods.
There are but two...
a god of light and love and joy
and a god of darkness,
evil, and fear.
Eternally at war.
There are no seven heavens
and no seven hells?
There's only one hell,
Princess.
The one we live in now.
Hodor.
Why did you wake me?
You've been gone for hours.
I was hungry.
We're all hungry.
I was just eating.
Summer was eating.
Your body can't live on
the food your wolf consumes.
Spending too much time in
Summer's skin is dangerous.
You're not a direwolf, Bran.
Must be glorious, though.
To run, to leap, to hunt.
To be whole.
I know that's tempting,
but if you're trapped
in Summer for too long,
you'll forget what it was
to be human.
You'd forget us, Bran.
You'd forget your mother
and father.
You'd forget your brothers
and sisters.
You'd forget Winterfell.
You'd forget you.
And if we lose you,
we lose everything.
Hodor, take me to the tree.
Look for me...
beneath the tree.
He saw us.
North.
I know where we have to go.
Let it be known
that Margaery of House Tyrell
and Joffrey of the Houses
Lannister and Baratheon
are one heart, one flesh,
one soul.
Cursed be he
who would seek
to tear them asunder.
With this kiss,
I pledge my love.
We have a new queen.
Better her than you.
- Bit much, wouldn't you say?
- It feels proportionate.
- Proportionate to what?
- The expected extravagance.
People who spend their money
on this sort of nonsense
tend not to have it for long.
You ought to try enjoying
something before you die.
You might find it suits you.
Not now, Mace. Lord Tywin
and I are speaking.
Anyway, I don't know what
you're complaining about.
I'm paying my share.
Shall we stick golden roses
in half the meat pies
to commemorate your generosity?
No, your heartfelt thank-you
is its own reward.
I would imagine I'd be hearing
it again before long.
Wars are rather expensive.
"The Iron Bank
will have its due."
How they love
to remind everyone.
Almost as much as you
Lannisters with your debts.
I'm not worried about
the Iron Bank.
We both know
you're smarter than that.
Come, Tywin, let us
celebrate young love.
All taken care of.
- You saw her board the ship?
- Aye, she's on it.
You saw the ship sail away?
No one knows she's there
but you, me, and Varys.
How do you know?
Because if someone follows
me without an invitation,
I'm the last person
they ever follow.
There's someone following you?
She's gone.
I know you don't want to
believe it, but she is.
Now, go drink till it feels
like you did the right thing.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Not you.
You look exquisite, child.
The wind has been
at you, though.
I haven't had the
opportunity to tell you
how sorry I was to hear
about your brother.
War is war, but killing
a man at a wedding,
horrid.
What sort of monster
would do such a thing?
As if men need more
reasons to fear marriage.
My lady.
Lord Tyrion, you see?
Not as bad as all that.
Perhaps if your pauper husband
were to sell his mule
and his last pair of shoes,
he might be able to afford to bring
you to Highgarden for a visit.
Now that peace has come and
all is right with the world,
it would do you good
to see some of it.
You must excuse me.
It's time I ate
some of this food I paid for.
♪ A coat of gold ♪
♪ Or a coat of red ♪
♪ A lion still has claws ♪
♪ And mine,
my lord... ♪
Very good. Very good.
Off you go.
My love, why don't we
make the announcement?
Everyone.
The queen would like
to say a few words.
We are so fortunate
to enjoy this marvelous
food and drink.
Not all among us are so lucky.
To thank the gods for bringing
the recent war to a just end,
King Joffrey has decreed
that the leftovers
from our feast be given
to the poorest in his city.
You're an example to us all.
Ser Jaime, I'm very sorry.
Ser Loras,
it's quite all right.
Your sister looks
very beautiful.
As does yours.
So, looking forward
to your wedding?
Yes, very much.
Our fathers are both
rather keen on the prospect.
They certainly are.
Perhaps they should
get married.
If you were to marry Cersei,
she'd murder you in your sleep.
If you somehow managed
to put a child in her first,
she'd murder him, too,
long before he drew
his first breath.
Luckily for you,
none of this will happen
because you'll never marry her.
And neither will you.
Your Grace.
My king.
- My queen.
- Lady Brienne.
So good of you to come.
I'm no lady, Your Grace.
Did you just bow?
Apologies, Your Grace.
I never did master the curtsy.
You're the one who put a sword
through Renly Baratheon.
That's not true, my love. Brienne
had nothing to do with it.
A shame.
I'd knight the man that put an
end to that deviant's life.
I just wanted
to congratulate you both
and wish you good fortune.
The country has been
at war too long.
I hope your reign
is long and peaceful.
- Yes, yes.
- Thank you.
I hope we see more of you.
Lady Brienne.
You're Lord Selwyn
Tarth's daughter.
That makes you a lady whether
you want to be or not.
As you say, Your Grace.
I owe you my gratitude.
You returned my brother
safely to King's Landing.
In truth, he rescued me,
Your Grace.
More than once.
Did he?
Haven't heard
that story before.
Not such a fascinating
story, I'm afraid.
I'm sure you have many
fascinating stories.
Sworn to Renly Baratheon. Sworn to Catelyn Stark.
And now my brother.
Must be exciting to flit
from one camp to the next
serving whichever lord
or lady you fancy.
I don't serve
your brother, Your Grace.
But you love him.
Your Grace.
No, no, come to my chambers and
I will examine you personally.
- She'll do no such thing.
- Oh, Your Grace.
Yes, well, this young
lady sought my advice...
You should see Qyburn.
He's quite good.
- Your Grace.
- Qyburn? Deplorable man.
Brought shame on the Citadel
with his repugnant experiments.
More repugnant than your gnarled
fingers on that girl's thighs?
Your Grace,
I am a man of learning.
My little brother had you sent to the
Black Cells when you annoyed him.
What do you think I could do
to you if you annoyed me?
I never meant to annoy anyone.
But you are.
You annoy me right now.
Every breath you draw
in my presence annoys me.
So here's what I want
you to do.
I want you to leave
my presence.
Leave this wedding right now.
Go to the kitchens
and instruct them
that all the leftovers from the feast
will be brought to the kennels.
Your Grace, Queen Margaery...
The queen is telling you
the leftovers
will feed the dogs
or you will.
A gold dragon to whoever
knocks my fool's hat off.
You're in rather a good mood.
- I suppose I am.
- I won't ask why.
- Small pleasures.
- Your Grace. Lord Tywin.
Prince Oberyn.
I don't believe you
have met Ellaria.
This is the Lord Hand
Tywin Lannister
and Cersei Lannister
the Queen Regent.
I suppose it is
former Queen Regent now.
Lord Hand and Lady Cersei,
- Ellaria Sand.
- My lord. My lady.
Charmed.
Can't say I've ever
met a Sand before.
We are everywhere in Dorne.
I have 10,000 brothers
and sisters.
Bastards are born
of passion, aren't they?
We don't despise them in Dorne.
No?
How tolerant of you.
I expect it is a relief,
Lady Cersei,
giving up your regal
responsibilities.
Wearing the crown for so many years
must have left your neck a bit crooked.
I suppose you'll never
know, Prince Oberyn.
It's a shame your older brother
couldn't attend the wedding.
Please give him our regards.
With any luck,
the gout will abate
with time and he will
be able to walk again.
They call it
the rich man's disease.
A wonder you don't have it.
Noblemen in my part
of the country
don't enjoy the same lifestyle
as our counterparts in Dorne.
People everywhere
have their differences.
In some places the highborn
frown upon those of low birth.
In other places the rape and
murder of women and children
is considered distasteful.
What a fortunate thing for
you, former Queen Regent,
that your daughter
Myrcella has been sent
to live in the latter
sort of place.
Everyone, silence!
Clear the floor.
There's been too much
amusement here today.
A royal wedding
is not an amusement.
A royal wedding is history.
The time has come for all of us
to contemplate our history.
My lords...
my ladies...
I give you
King Joffrey...
Renly, Stannis,
Robb Stark, Balon Greyjoy.
The War of the Five Kings.
I'm the rightful king.
- King in the North!
- Yes!
Traitor. You're a traitor.
For the Seven Kingdoms!
Let the war begin.
Renly, you're no king.
Away, degenerate.
Away. Away.
Ooh, careful.
- Go on.
- I want you to be my prince.
Stannis!
Who's got the gold now, Stark?
I am the rightful king.
Challenge me, ruffian.
- Take that.
- I'm drowning. I'm drowning.
I am the King in the North!
Not wildfire!
Pay each of them 20 gold
when this is done.
Yes, my lord.
We'll have to find another
way to thank the king.
Charge!
Ready, again.
I am the King in the North!
- Charge!
Yes!
Your head!
Fine gentlemen.
Well fought.
Here you are.
Champion's purse.
Though you're not
the champion yet, are you?
A true champion defeats
all the challengers.
Surely there are
others out there
who still dare
to challenge my reign.
Uncle.
How about you? I'm sure
they have a spare costume.
One taste of combat was
enough for me, Your Grace.
I would like to keep
what remains of my face.
I think you should fight him.
This was but a poor imitation
of your own bravery
on the field of battle.
I speak as a firsthand witness.
Climb down from the high table
with your new Valyrian sword
and show everyone how
a true king wins his throne.
Be careful, though.
This one is clearly
mad with lust.
It would be a tragedy for
the king to lose his virtue
hours before his wedding night.
A fine vintage.
Shame that it spilled.
It did not spill.
My love, come back to me.
It's time for
my father's toast.
Well, how does he expect me
to toast without wine?
Uncle, you can be my cupbearer
seeing as you're
too cowardly to fight.
Your Grace does me
a great honor.
It's not meant as an honor.
Bring me my goblet.
What good is an empty cup?
Fill it.
Kneel.
Kneel before your king.
I said...
kneel!
Look, the pie.
My queen.
Wonderful.
My hero.
- Can we leave now?
- Let's find out.
Uncle.
Where are you going?
You're my cupbearer, remember?
I thought I might change out of
these wet clothes, Your Grace.
No, no, no. No, you're
perfect the way you are.
Serve me my wine.
Well, hurry up.
This pie is dry.
Mm, good.
Needs washing down.
If it please Your Grace,
Lady Sansa is very tired.
No.
No, you'll wait here...
un...
Your Grace?
It's nothing.
- He's choking!
- Help the poor boy.
- Idiots, help your king.
- Move away!
- Joffrey! Joffrey!
- Help him!
- Someone help him!
- Joffrey!
- Come with me now.
- Joffrey! Joffrey!
If you want to live,
we have to leave.
Don't touch him!
Joffrey.
Please, Joffrey.
Joffrey, what is it?
Help him!
My son.
He's gone.
Our king is gone.
He did this.
He poisoned my son,
your king.
Take him.
Take him!
♪ In a coat of gold ♪
♪ Or a coat of red ♪
♪ A lion still has claws ♪
♪ And mine are long ♪
♪ And sharp, my lord ♪
♪ As long and sharp as yours ♪
♪ And so he spoke
and so he spoke ♪
♪ That Lord of Castamere ♪
♪ And now the rains ♪
♪ Weep o'er his hall ♪
♪ With no one there to hear ♪
♪ Yes, now the rains ♪
♪ Weep o'er his hall ♪
♪ And not a soul
to hear. ♪